<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
 
 <title>BLOG_NAME</title>
 <link href="YOUR_URL/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="YOUR_URL"/>
 <updated>2013-03-25T23:18:13+11:00</updated>
 <id>BLOG_URL</id>
 <author>
   <name>BLOG_NAME</name>
 </author>

 
 <entry>
   <title>Finally got Jekyll running</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/second-post.html"/>
   <updated>2013-03-25T00:00:00+11:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/second-post</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;After an intense code sprint, I finally got Jekyll running as my blog engine. From this point on, its Markdown for blogposts and git commit to publish :)&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Portfolio</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/portfolio.html"/>
   <updated>2013-03-25T00:00:00+11:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/portfolio</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;This portfolio page is coming soon!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>About Yoongfook</title>
   <link href="YOUR_URL/about.html"/>
   <updated>2013-03-25T00:00:00+11:00</updated>
   <id>BLOG_URL/about</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I am am an experienced &lt;a href=&quot;#prod&quot;&gt;product manager&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;#dev&quot;&gt;ruby on rails programmer&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;#design&quot;&gt;front-end designer&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;#startup&quot;&gt;startup founder&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Product Manager&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am currently a &lt;a href=&quot;http://pollenizer.com/what-is-a-lean-product-manager&quot;&gt;Lean Product Manager&lt;/a&gt; at &lt;a href=&quot;http://pollenizer.com&quot;&gt;Pollenizer&lt;/a&gt;, one of the top startup incubator in Australia. This role has a good overlap between customer development and product management. We use &lt;a href=&quot;http://theleanstartup.com/&quot;&gt;lean startup&lt;/a&gt; principles - running experiments, measuring results, hacking growth, &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Agile_software_development&quot;&gt;agile dev&lt;/a&gt; and quick iterations.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Ruby on Rails Programmer&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been writing apps with Ruby on Rails since 2011 and started doing commercial freelancing work in 2012. The most recent project is &lt;a href=&quot;http://singaporetender.com&quot;&gt;Singapore Tender&lt;/a&gt; where I implemented a role-based authentication system (Devise, CanCan),  account activation system, nested model forms, image uploading (CarrierWave), daily email digests, paypal integration (ActiveMerchant),  object-based searching (Ransack), and email campaign integration (Gibbon).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Front-end Designer&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I use the latest in CSS technology (&lt;a href=&quot;http://sass-lang.com&quot;&gt;SASS&lt;/a&gt; - mixins, variables, &lt;a href=&quot;http://twitter.github.com/bootstrap&quot;&gt;Twitter Bootstrap&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://foundation.zurb.com&quot;&gt;Zurb Foundation&lt;/a&gt;), and popular Javascript frameworks (&lt;a href=&quot;http://jquery.com&quot;&gt;jQuery&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://angularjs.org&quot;&gt;Angular JS&lt;/a&gt;) to create modern-looking websites at a fraction of the time needed. As the saying goes- don't re-invent the wheel.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Startup Founder&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started 3 businesses in Singapore before moving to Sydney. Tagloop - An online store for pre-programmed NFC stickers, Gspot - A platform for launching referral campaigns on Facebook, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://hastify.com&quot;&gt;Hastify&lt;/a&gt; - An online food delivery website. At Hastify, we managed to raise $50,000 from the Singaporean Government, and subsequently an angel round from one of the founders of &lt;a href=&quot;http://hungrygowhere.com&quot;&gt;Hungrygowhere&lt;/a&gt;, the Yelp of Singapore&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>